{
    "subject": "resource/Basler_Zeitung",
    "predicate": "ontology/language",
    "object": "resource/German_language",
    "human_readable": "The language of Basler Zeitung is German.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7964637875556946,
            "question": "What language does Basler Zeitung use?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6071518659591675,
            "question": "Is Basler Zeitung published in English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43869414925575256,
            "question": "In what country is Basler Zeitung likely published?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3575804531574249,
            "question": "What is the history of the German language?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32983022928237915,
            "question": "Is German a widely spoken language in Europe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19410575926303864,
            "question": "What other types of media use the German language?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09677285701036453,
            "question": "What are some examples of German literature?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.0827409029006958,
            "question": "What are some popular German newspapers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.052345145493745804,
            "question": "What language is commonly spoken in Basel, Switzerland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.04091827943921089,
            "question": "Are there any other Swiss newspapers published in German?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The language of Basler Zeitung is German.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8525_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What language is commonly spoken in Basel, Switzerland?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8525_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular German newspapers?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8525_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some examples of German literature?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8525_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8525_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8525_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8525_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8525_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8525_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8525_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8525_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8525_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8525_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8525_66.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. According to the text, the newspaper \"Basler Zeitung\" has a language of \"Deutch\", which is translated to English as \"German\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe context information clearly states that the \"Basler Zeitung\" newspaper \"Language: Deutch (German)\", which supports the query that the language of Basler Zeitung is German."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}